spriters-resource.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - The Spriters Resource

The VG Resource cares about your privacy:

• We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.  
• We will not share your contact information with another user without your consent.  
• We will make a reasonable effort to secure your information in our databases with industry-standard technologies.

If we change our privacy policy, we will notify you by sending the changes to you, or publishing the changes on our site.

Information Collection

Registration  
In order to become a member of The VG Resource, you must provide us with a valid email address, an identitying name ("username") and a password. If you were invited to The VG Resource by another member, we will also record who sent you the original invitation.

Invitations  
If you invite another person to become a member of The VG Resource, we will send that person an e-mail with a personalized invitation from you. This email will contain your e-mail address. To confirm that invitations are accepted by the intended individual, we maintain a record of the e-mail addresses of the sender and recipient of invitations. We do not use this information for any purpose other than verifying invitation acceptance.

Profile  
The VG Resource allows you to personalize your profile page. You may include information such as an avatar to represent yourself, a signature to close off all posts made on the forums or other descriptions. Any information you place in your profile is publicly viewable by other users of The VG Resource unless set to private or otherwise stated. All profile information may be deleted or modified by you. Aside from our backup files, we do not maintain records of your deleted information. We do not share any profile information with other companies that includes any of your personally-identifying information.

Instant Messengers  
You may include information such as your identity in instant-messaging services within The VG Resource. This information is purely optional. If you provide this information, other members of The VG Resource will be able to contact you through these instant-messenger services by clicking on the appropriate links on your profile page. If you do not wish them to do so, you may delete this information at any time.

Email Contact  
You may also choose to allow other members of The VG Resource to contact you via e-mail. If you do, members will be able to fill out a form to send you a message to your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is not disclosed to them when this happens, but they may learn your address if you choose to respond. By the same token, if you send an e-mail address to another member who has enabled the e-mail contact option, your e-mail address will be revealed to them. You may enable or disable the "contact via email" option at any time.

Cookies  
The VG Resource depends on cookies to maintain sessions with our users, to enable you to resume your login on subsequent visits, and to store other pieces of information that are necessary for the proper operation and customization of our applications.

We also use cookies through third-party vendors including Google to serve ads. These cookies enable Google and its partners to serve ads based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the internet. You may opt out of Google's personalized advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Logs  
We maintain logs that record the Internet Protocol (IP) address of all incoming connections, the pages that visitors view, database queries performed, and the parts of applications that are utilized. We use this information to understand usage patterns and to improve our service. We do not share this information with any other company.

Advertisements  
We may include advertisements on The VG Resource for services or products we offer, as well as services and products offered by other companies. These advertisements may target a particular set of users (for example, those who have expressed interest in RPG games might receive more advertisements related to RPGs). We do not provide any personally-identifying information to the advertising servers or agencies that display these advertisements.

Information Use

The VG Resource includes services that are intended to help users form and maintain friendships with other users. As such, the information you provide is intended to describe yourself to other users. Any information that you provide that does not personally identify you (such as usage patterns, information about pages you visit, and so forth) may be used by The VG Resource for any reason, in its sole discretion.

The VG Resource may contact you with newsletters, promotional information or other things relating to the service. You may opt-out of this communication by unchecking the appropriate e-mail contact option on your account information. You may still receive contact from us regarding the proper functioning and/or security of your account.

Information Sharing

We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. 

When you customize your profile on The VG Resource, you are making this information publicly available. You can always delete the information you provide, but it is possible that some of this information might be retained by third-party search engines.

We may provide aggregate information, such as demographic, psychographic and page viewing preference information to third parties as we deem appropriate. This information will never contain personally-identifying information.

When you send instant-messages or e-mails to other members through the service, your own instant-messaging information and e-mail contact information will be provided to those members. Any further communication between yourself and that member is subject to whatever privacy and security functions are present within your e-mail and instant messaging programs.

If you have questions or comments about the The VG Resource privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using the designated contact page.
